foreign
[Music]
there is still quite a bit of snow on
the ground despite the first days of
spring that I can sense my little Valley
is starting to wake up after five sleepy
months of snow and ice
the warmth in the air couldn't be more
welcomed and despite the mud on my boots
I'm in High Spirits and anticipating the
first spring flowers
I still have a while to wait but the new
season is moving in the air has shifted
smells of fresh soil and saplings
permeate the forest
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
this is a time of great change in my
quiet secluded life
I have great plans of future gardening
projects hiking on Trails newly
uncovered and as promised the
announcement of some new additions to my
animal family
[Music]
wood was full of rabbit holes and in the
neatest sandiest told the ball lived
Benjamin's aunt and his cousins flopsy
mopsy Cottontail and Peter old Mrs
rabbit was a widow she earned her living
by knitting rabbit wool mittens and
muffets I once bought a pair at a Bazaar
she also sold herbs and rosemary tea and
rabbit tobacco which is what we call
lavender
foreign
[Music]
Bernard two sweet little rabbits that
have recently found their way into my
life
once they're old enough they will be
living together in a little rabbit
dwelling my husband and I are building
in the spring in the meantime they're
getting used to all the new smells and
sounds of the cottage safely tucked away
in a little indoor Hutch they're already
bringing me great joy adding a new
vibrancy into my cold and snowy world
I recently decided to make a little
porch Garden of herbs and flowers and a
vegetable garden in front of my home
with great plans to grow more mint and
chamomile for tea
I used to dislike this time of year
somewhere between winter and spring when
all you see is mud and dead grass mixed
in with melting snow
and yet now I like to see it as a
necessary time as we all must accept
seasons of scarcity in order to truly
enjoy the abundance that is yet to come
cloudy and dark days are perhaps not so
bad as we think because they always give
way to something beautiful if we are
only patient
foreign
[Music]
I think I still have mud on me it is so
swampy and wet outside but I have to
admit I'm really enjoying it because I
am so ready for spring it's been I think
almost five months of snow and that is a
much longer winter than we're used to
and so I just I just I'm impatient but
I'm trying to be patient so yes we did
invite two lovely new bunnies to come
live with us Luke and I are gonna work
on building a wonderful outdoor
Sanctuary for them for the spring and if
you happen to know where the names
Bianca and Bernard come from do let me
know it is one of my favorite sets of
movies so of course there is a lot of
change on the horizon change of seasons
new bunnies new things to build around
the house sales from my Etsy shop this
week will be helping go towards building
Bernard and Bianca's new outdoor
Sanctuary hopefully it can be a place to
bring rescued rabbits in the future as
well and so I have big plans rabbits
have always been one of my favorite
types of animals I think that they are
so sweet and so deeply affected by their
environment if they're in a chaotic and
Loud environment it is quite difficult
for them to thrive and they really crave
peace and nature and quietness and I
feel like our souls are quite similar in
that way so I'm a huge fan of bunnies
and I'm so happy to have more in my life
if flowers are blooming and things are
bright and blue where you are that is so
wonderful please send some of that
lovely warmth and Magic over here but
the snow will be melted soon I am sure
sending all my love I will see you very
soon
[Music]
thank you
foreign